Guide to the Records of the Women's Philharmonic M1470
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series V: Development: Grants/Giving
  - Subseries III: Corporate Sponsorship
    - AETNA (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - American Express (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - AMFAC (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Apple, Inc. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Arts Recovery Fund (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Astral Foundation (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Atkinson Foundation (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Bechtel Foundation (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Blue Cross (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Bohannon Foundation (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Bothin Helping Fund (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Buttes Gas and Oil (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Cal Humanities (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Corporate Funders (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Corporate Fundraising (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Corporate Sponsorship Opening Night FY 01 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Hewlett Foundation (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Hewlett-Packard Foundation (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Phillip Morris, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Bette Clark/McMurray Foundation (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Life (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Neiman Marcus (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Open Meadows (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Packard (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Penninsula Community Foundation (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Planned Giving (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Sarah Lee (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Shaklee (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Skaggs (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Security Pacific (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Syntex (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - US Air (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Wattis Foundation (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Eastman Kodak Co. (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Macy's West (Box 134, Folders 1)
    - Meadowood (St. Helena, CA) (Box 134, Folders 2)
    - Mervyn's (Box 134, Folders 3)
    - Met Life (Box 134, Folders 4)
    - Morrison & Foerster (Box 134, Folders 5)
    - Oracle (Box 134, Folders 6)
    - Peet's Coffee and Tea (Box 134, Folders 7)
    - The Gap (Box 134, Folders 8)
    - Genentech (Box 134, Folders 9)
    - Ghilotti Bros. Construction (Box 134, Folders 10)
    - Goldman Sachs Fund (Box 134, Folders 11)
    - Hewlett-Packard (Box 134, Folders 12)
    - IBM (Box 134, Folders 13)
    - Levi Strauss (Box 134, Folders 14)
    - Long's Drug Stores (Box 134, Folders 15)
    - Jessica McClintock (Box 134, Folders 16)
    - Johnson Publishing Co. (Box 134, Folders 17)
    - Mattel, Inc. (Box 134, Folders 18)
    - Calyx & Corolla (Box 134, Folders 19)
    - Clorox (Box 134, Folders 20)
    - Cybercash (Box 134, Folders 21)
    - Deloitte & Touche (Box 134, Folders 22)
    - DFS Group Ltd. (Box 134, Folders 23)
    - Ernst & Young, LLP (Box 134, Folders 24)
    - Discovery Toys (Box 134, Folders 25)
    - Ellis Chevrolet (Box 134, Folders 26)
    - Emerson Electric (Box 134, Folders 27)
    - Esprit (Box 134, Folders 28)
    - Fair Isaac (Box 134, Folders 29)
    - Gannett Communities FUnd (Box 134, Folders 30)
    - Birkenstock (Box 134, Folders 31)
    - BRE Properties (Box 134, Folders 32)
    - Chevron (Box 134, Folders 33)
    - Prospects Corporate (Box 134, Folders 34)
    - Corporate Inquiries, 93-94 (Box 134, Folders 35)
    - Corporate Solicitations workshop through Arts Management Inst. 8/97 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Alumnae resources (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - American Center for Wine, Food, and the Arts (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - AMEX (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - American Express: Arts marketing (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Anheuser-Busch Companies (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Arco (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - AT&T (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Autodesk (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Bank of CA (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Bay Area Women owned businesses (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Bay View Bank (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - SMI Hotels (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Target Stores (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Texaco Foundation (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Transamerica (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - USL Capital (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - VISA (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Wells Fargo (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Westinghouse Foundation (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Women for Winesense (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Working Assets (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - WorldCom (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Pac Bell / Telesis 1995 (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - PG&E (Box 139, Folder 17)
    - Philip Morris - matching gifts (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - Potlatch (Box 139, Folder 19)
    - Premier U. S. travel (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Purple Moon (Box 139, Folder 21)
    - RJR Nabisco (Box 139, Folder 22)
    - San Jose Lasers (Box 139, Folder 23)
    - Schwab (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Scios - Nova (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Simpson Paper (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Support: Shaklee (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Bank of America (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Corporate rejects (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Subseries IV: Grants for the Arts
    - Grants for the Arts 83-84 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Grants for the Arts 84-85 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Grants for the Arts (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Grants for the Arts 85-86 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Grants for the Arts 86-87 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Grant for the Arts (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Grants for the Arts 88-89 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - GFTA, 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - GFTA, 1991-1992 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - GFTA, 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - GFTA, 1993-1994 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - GFTA, 1994-1995 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - GFTA, 1995-1996 (Part I) (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - GFTA, 1995-1996 (Part II) (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - GFTA, 1997-1998 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - GFTA, 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - GFTA, 1999-2000 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - GFTA, 2000-2001 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - GFTA: Non-recurring event fund (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - GFTA, 1996-1997 (Part I) (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - GFTA, 1996-1997 (Part II) (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - GFTA, 2000-2001 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - GFTA, 2003-2004 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - GFTA, 2002-2003 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - GFTA Billing - Instructions/Info (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Grants for Arts, 2003-2004 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Grants for the Arts (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Subseries V: Meet the Composer Grant
    - Meet the Composer (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Meet the Composer New Residencies 1999-2001 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Meet the Composer 1998 International Creative Collaborations (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Meet the Composer; Music Alive; L. Karpman 200-2001 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Meet the Composer Fund 2000-2001 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Meet the Composer-1998-1999 Season (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Meet the Composer, Music Alive 2000 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Meet the Composer: New Residencies 09/1999 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Meet the Composer Commissioning 1998 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Meet the Composer 1993 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Meet the Composer 2002/2003 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Meet the Composer: Tina Davidson (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Meet the Composer Consortium: Hankinson (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Meet the Composer--Participant in Consortium Commission Ekizian (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Meet the Composer: Barnwell Sweet Honey (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Meet the Composer Guidelines 1996 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Meet the Composer 1994 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Meet the Composer: New Residences (Part II) (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Meet the Composer California (part I) (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Meet the Composer California (Part II) (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Meet the Composer: Tania Leon (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Meet the Composer Cosortium (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Meet the Composer consortium: Shulimet Ran, composer (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Meet the Composer residencies 1995-1998 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Meet the Composer: new residences (Part I) (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Meet the Composer/ASOL (American Symphony Orchestra League) July 1999 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Meet the Composer, 2001 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Meet the Composer report, 1994 (Box 150, Folder 18)
  - Subseries VI: National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)
    - NEA Access 2003-04 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - NEA Advancement (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - NEA (development) (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - NEA Financial Status Report (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - NEA Grants (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - NEA Grant 1993 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - NEA New Music Ensembles (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - NEA Creative Projects 88-89 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - NEA Orchestras 85-86 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - NEA Orchestras 86-87 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - NEA Orchestras 87-88 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - NEA Orchestras 88-89 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - NEA Orchestras 89-90 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - NEA orchestras 1994-1995 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - NEA orchestra application 1995-1996 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - NEA orchestras 1996-1998 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - NEA Services to Composers 86-87 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - NEA Services to Composers 87-88 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - NEA Services to Composers 88-89 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - NEA Services to Composers 89-90 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - NEA Challenge III application materials (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - NEA Challenge III reports (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - NEA Challenge IV (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - 1993 NEA documentation (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - NEA Challenge guidelines 1996 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - NEA composer fellowships (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - 1993 NEA composer in residence (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - NEA-creative projects 1993-1996 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - NEA creative projects 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - NEA creative projects 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - NEA budget cuts: press + information (1995-1997) (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - NEA: education + access grants (1998) (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - NEA March 1995 grants status (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - NEA general information (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - NEA millenium materials (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - NEA music recording 1995-1997 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - NEA new structure notes (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - NEA award information 1993 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - NEA orchestras 1993-1994 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - NEA orchestra 1991-1992 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - NEA pilot orchestra education 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - NEA services to composers 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - NEA services to composers 1993-1994 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - NEA services to composers 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - NEA services to composers 1992-1993 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - NEA services to composers 1991-1992 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - NEA services to composers 1990-1991 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - NEA signature authorization form (July 1999) (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - NEA special projects 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - NEA total funding history (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - NEA 1997-1998 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - NEA 1998 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - NEA Planning + Stabilization May 1998 - June 2000 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - NEA Funding 1998 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - NEA Resources for Change: Technology 2001 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - NEA: 2001-2002 Grant Guidelines (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - NEA: Creativity, FY 2002 application (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - NEA Access: FY 2001 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - NEA Creation and Presentation: Fanfares (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - NEA Creation and Presentation: Fanfares II (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - NEA Education (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - NEA Financial Status Report, 2002 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - NEA Heritage and Preservation as of 8/1998 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - NEA Heritage and Preservation contract (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - NEA Heritage and Preservation (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - NEA Education, 2000 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - NEA Presentation, 2000 American Women's Masters Series (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - NEA Presentation Report (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - NEA, 1999 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - NEA Advertising Logo (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - NEA: 2000 National Medal of Arts nomination (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - NEA: Authorization forms (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - NEA: Access, 2001 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Subseries VII: San Francisco Arts Commission
    - San Francisco Foundation 1981-1984 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco Foundation 2003 (Box 76)
    - San Francisco Foundation 2003 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - San Francisco Foundation 2002-2003 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco Foundation 2001-2002 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - San Francisco Foundation 2000 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Foundation Grant 1999 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco Foundation 1996-1999 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco Foundation 1990-1991 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Foundation 1988-1989 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Arts Commission Organization Project Grants 2002/2003 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Cultural Equity Grants Program 2001-2002 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco CEI Level Two Letter of intent April 6, 2001 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - SF Cultural Equity Grants program July 2000 grant (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - SF Cultural Equity Initiative (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco Commission on Status of Women grant award January 1997 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Cultural Equity Grant Financial report 1999 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Sponsors list and SFAC grant, 2000-2001 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - SFAC guidelines, 2003/2004 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Subseries VIII: Miscellaneous Grant/Fund files
    - 1999-2000 Misc Grants (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ACORN Grant 1983 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Acquisition Campaign (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Community Development Block Grant (CDBG) (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Community Development Block Grant (CDBG) Workplan (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Cone FND (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Consolidated Capital (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Contents of old fundraising packet (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Mary Crocker (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Development (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Ditson (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Ditson Fund (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Donations (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Max + Victoria Dreyfus (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - East Bay Community Foundation (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Fleishacker as of 2002 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Geraldine C. and Emory M. Ford Foundation (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - General Services Foundation (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Gifts in Honor of: (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Global Fund for Women 1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - William Irwin Foundation (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Joint Foundation (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Jr League (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Kinsely Family Trust (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Lakeside Foundation (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Levi Strauss Foundation (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - McKesson Fund (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 3/8/2001 Spaulding Fundraiser (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Fanancial and Grant information (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Photo Releases (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - SF Education Fund (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - SFAC-OPG 2003-04 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Request statistics for Lenders 1995 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Women-owned Restaurants (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Whitaker 2003-04 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - GFTA Vol. Arts Contr. Fund 2004 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Guide for Orchestra Advocates (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Major Donors Checks Checklist 98-99 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Equities Initiative Grant Billing 1999 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Mikhashoff Trust for New Music (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - F. Miller Foundation (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Montgomery Street Foundation (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Ruth Mott Fund (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - National Arts Stabilization Fund (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - NYU Center for Women in Music Award (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Northern California Grantmakers Presentation 1998 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Osher Foundation 2002 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Open Meadows Foundations 2002 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - David and Lucille Packard Foundation 1998 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Ralp M. Parsons Foundation (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Peninsula Community Foundation (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - PEW Charitable Trusts (Part 1) (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - PEW Charitable Trusts (Part II) (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Philharmonic Ventures Foundation (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Prospectus (early) (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Roberts Foundation (new) (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Recording Academy (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Foundation General Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller Phase I (1991) (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller Phase II (1992-1993) (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller MAP 1992 & earlier (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Rockefeller MAP 1993 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller MAP 1995/1996 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller MAP 1996/1997 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Rockefeller 1997/1998 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Rockefeller MAP 1999 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Rockefeller MAP 2001 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Gerbode Foundation (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Global Fund for Women (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Richard and Rhoda Goldman Fund (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Florence Gould Foundation (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Grawemeyer Music Award (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Guzik Foundation (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Haas Creative Work Fund (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Luke B. Hancock Foundation (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Harmony Fund (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - William Randoplh Hearst Foundation (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Clarence E. Heller Foundation (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Hewlett Foundation, February 2001, 3 year proposal (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - William and Flora Hewlett Foundation (Part II) (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Horizons (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Jacqueline Hume (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - James Irvine Foundation (Part I) (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - James Irvin Foundation (Part II) (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Willian G. Irwin Charity foundation (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Jerome Foundation (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Jewett Foundation (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Jewish Community Endowment Fund (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Junior League (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Kerr Foundation (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Knight Foundation (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Koussevitzky-Tannaka 2001 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Koussevitzky Music Foundation (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - LEF Foundation (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Limited/NPR Project (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Management Center (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Marin Community Foundation (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - MacArthur Foundation (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - McKesson Foundation 12/1997 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - California council for the Humanities information (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Harvest Works (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Fundraising Profile 10/1999 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Whitaker (Part II) 1995 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Whitaker Fund Materials 1991 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Whitaker 2000 - 2001 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Whitaker (Part I) 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Current Grant Obligations 2000 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Recent Grants to Orchestras 1999 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Cindi Hubbard development briefing February 2000 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - 2000 - 2001 Season Sponsorships (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Financial Development (2000) materials (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Pacific Telesis Grant May 2 1998 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Financial Year (FY) 2001: Grant Action Calendars (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - American Composers Forum funding 2000 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Ames Family Fund (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - American Express Philanthropic Program 1999 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Animating Democracy 2000 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Animating Democracy 2001 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Animating Democracy materials 2000 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Arts and Business council 2000 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Astraea - Nat'l Lesbian Action Foundation (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Barlow Foundation (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Baker Street Foundation (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Barkley Fund (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - BMI Foundation (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Bay Area Performing Arts Scholarship Program (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Carol Franc Buck Foundation (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - The Carlyle Fund (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Robert sterling Clark Foundation (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Columbia (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Compton (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Aaron Copland Fund for Music (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Aaron Copland Fund (supplemental 2002 - 2003) (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Aaron Copland supplemental 2001-2002 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Copland Performing ensembles 2001 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Copland Performing ensembles 2000 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Aaron Copland fund for music (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Aaron Copland performing fund (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Aaron Copland recording fund (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Creative Work Fund (Haas) 1996-1997 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Creative Work fund (Haas) 1997-1998 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Creative Work Fun (Haas) 1995-1996 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Louise M. Davis Foundation (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Cummings (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Doris Duke Charitable Foundation (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - East Bay Community Foundation (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Eastman Fund (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Fleishacker Foundation (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Audience Development initiative: Fleishacker Foundation (Part I) (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Audience Development Initiative: Fleishacker Foundation (Part II) (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Fireman's Fund (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Ford Foundation (Part I) (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation (Part II) (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Fort Mason Foundation (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Gateway Initiative (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Geraldine and Emory Ford Foundation (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Fred Gellert Foundation (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Ann and Gordon Getty (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Event Goers (donor invitation list) August 1996 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Grant ideas (1994-1997) (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - ANG Network (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - California Lawyers for the Arts (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Ramona Galey (2nd trumpeter) Donation Appeal + correspondence (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Asian Cultural Council grant inquiry 2001 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Association of California Symphony Orchestras: 2000 Most Valuable Player Award (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Audit (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Grant invoicing to do list: 1998-1999 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Women's Phil. Audit reports 1996-2000 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Cindi Hubbard: misc funding correspondence 2001 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 2001-2002 Budget materials (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - William and Flora Hewlett Foundation Grant report 2002 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Planned Giving: list of donors (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Planned Giving resources 2000 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - SF Foundation, 1985-1987 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Sister Fund (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Skaggs Foundation (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - The Society for American Music (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Stuart Foundation (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Stulsaft (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Thendara Foundation (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - S. Mark Taper fund (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Tides Foundation (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Artists Fund (for International Festivals) (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Van Loben Sels (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Vanguard (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Mellon (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - SF Foundation, 1992-1995 (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Lila Wallace - Reader Digest Foundation (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Vienna Midern Masters (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Lila Wallace, 2003/2004 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Women's Foundation (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Zellerbach (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Earned Income Projects Development (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Stock Market (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Financials 1999-2000 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Matching Gifts - Pending (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Matching Gifts - Processed (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Copland Grant (Box 141, Folder 13)